The reason I asked you to brunch...
너희들을 불러낸 이유는
is because I've been thinking
about my maid of honor.
내 신부 들러리를 누구로
할까 생각중이거든
Oh, my God. This is it. Oh.
어머나, 이 순간이야
I hope it's you.
너이길 바래
-I hope it's you.
-Me too.
- 너이길 바래
- 나두
First of all,
I love you both so much.
우선
너희 둘 다 많이 사랑해
-You're both so important to me.
-Blah, blah, blah. Who is it?
- 내겐 중요한 친구들이야
- 어쩌구 저쩌구, 누구야?
I was thinking we could
come up with a system...
방식을 생각해 냈는데
where we trade off
being maid of honor.
차례대로 하기로 하자구
-Hypothetically, if Phoebe were mine..
-Yes! Oh.
- 피비가 가정으로 나의...
- 좋아라!
Hypothetically.
가정이야
Still.
그래두
If Phoebe were mine, Rachel would
be Phoebe's, I'd be Rachel's.
피비가 나의, 레이첼은 피비의
난 레이첼의 들러리로
We all get to do it
and no one gets upset.
마음 상하는 일없이
모두 순서가 돌아오잖아
-That's a pretty good idea.
-I'll do that. So, who's yours?
- 좋은 생각 같은데
- 그렇게 하자, 이번은 누가해?
Well, that's the best part.
You guys get to decide.
가장 좋은 부분인데
너희들이 정하는거야
-Why is that the best part?
-I don't have to.
- 그게 왜 가장 좋은 부분이야?
- 내가 안해도 되잖아
Of course we'll help you decide.
We'll do anything we can to help you.
물론 정하는 걸 도와주지
뭐든 최선을 다해 도울게
I'd like to make a toast.
건배나 하자구
To the future Mrs. Chandler Bing...
챈들러 빙의
부인이 될 사람을 위하여
my best friend and truly one
of the nicest people that..
나의 가장 친한 친구
세상에서 제일 착한...
-Really not deciding.
-Fine.
- 내가 선택 안 해
- 알았어
Excuse me,
I couldn't help overhearing.
실례합니다
엿듣는 건 아니었지만
-You're marrying Chandler Bing?
-Yeah.
- 챈들러 빙과 결혼한다구요?
- 맞아요
Good luck!
행운을 비네요!
Oh, and good luck to you too!
그 쪽도 행운을 빌어요!
What a nice lady.
참 착한 분이시네
The One With Nap Partners
Yeah!
그래!
-Die Hard, still great.
-Yep.
- 다이 하드, 아직도 멋있어
- 그러게 말이다
영화 한 편 더 볼까?
Let's make it a double feature?
또 뭘 빌렸는데?
What else you rent?
다이 하드 2
Die Hard 2.
조이, 이것도 1편이잖아
Joey, this is Die Hard 1 again.
두 번 보면
다이 하드 2가 되는거지
Well, we'll watch it a second time
and it's Die Hard 2.
- 방금 본거잖아
- 그래서?
-Joey, we just saw it.
-And?
그래서 또 보자구!
It would be cool to see it again!
- 그래! 다이 하드!
- 다이 하드!
-Yeah! Die Hard!
-Die Hard!
다이 하드라고
왜 안했지?
Dude, you didn't say Die Hard.
괜찮은거야?
Is everything okay?
응, 약속이 있어서...
Yeah, I just got plans.
존 맥클레인도
약속이 있었지
Well, John McClane had plans.
조이가 흥분해서
'계집애'라고 부르기 전에
I want to leave before
Joey gets all worked up...
그만 갈려구
and starts calling
everybody "bitch."
무슨 소리를 하는거야
계집애야?
What are you talking about, bitch?
- 레이첼
- 그래
-Hey, Rachel.
-Yeah?
내가 결혼할때 내
신부 들러리가 되어 줄래?
When I get married,
will you be my maid of honor?
정말?
Really?
어머나, 피비
무슨 말을 해야...
Oh, my God, Phoebe.
I mean I'm just..
잠깐만
Wait a minute.
그럼 네가 모니카의
들러리가 되잖아
If I'm your maid of honor,
that means that you are Monica's.
그런건가
Oh.
그렇게 하고 싶으면
그러자
Well, if that's what you want.
말도 안 돼
내가 모니카 들러리 할래
No way, Phoebe.
I want to be Monica's.
- 왜 그렇게 중요해?
- 너한텐 왜 중요한건데?
-Why does it even matter?
-Why does it matter to you?
현재의 일이니까
Because this one is now.
걔네 둘 다 친한 친구잖아
And it's two of our best friends.
넌 누구와 결혼할지
알게 뭐야
And who knows what you're gonna marry.
로스와 결혼하면?
조이와 하면?
What if I marry Ross? or Joey?
조이는 허락 못해
You wouldn't.
레이첼, 너가
정말로 하고 싶은 건 알아
Okay, look, Rachel.
I know you really want to do this...
하지만 난 한 번도
들러리 못 서봤어
but I've never been
maid of honor to anyone before.
넌 2번이나 해 봤잖아
I know you've done it at least twice.
- 그렇지만 피비...
- 끝까지 들어봐
-Yeah, but Phoebe..
-Please let me finish.
아니, 그게 다야
I guess that was it.
알았어
Okay.
안 해봤다니까
네가 모니카의 들러리다
Since you've never done it before,
you can be Monica's maid of honor.
정말로 고맙다!
Oh, thank you so much!
좋아라
Yay.
난 아주 괜찮은
사람이랑 결혼할거야
I'm gonna marry someone good.
알고 있어
Oh, I know.
챈들러보다 훨 나은 사람이랑
Better than Chandler.
- 어떻게 된거야?
- 몰라
-What happened?
-I don't know.
We fell asleep. That is all.
잠들었던 것 뿐이야
Yeah. Yeah? Yeah.
맞아, 맞는 말이야
All right, well, I'd better go.
가야 되겠어
-I think that would be best.
-Yeah.
- 좋은 생각이야
- 그래
-I'll talk to you later.
-Okay.
- 나중에 얘기하자
- 알았어
-But not about this.
-No, never. Never!
- 이 일에 관해선 말구
- 절대로 말 안 하기!
-Bye.
-No touch. No touch.
- 안녕
- 만지지마
브런치 도중에
별난 일이 있었어
Hey, a weird thing happened at brunch.
자기랑 결혼한다는 걸
무심코 들은 여자가
This woman overheard that
I was marrying you...
나한테 행운을 빌더라구
and she wished me good luck.
좋은 사람이네
That's sweet.
그런 뜻이 아니라
'잘 해 봐라' 같았어
No, it was more like a "good luck."
어떻게 생긴 여자였는데?
So, what did this woman look like?
한 서른 살에
검정색 머리, 이뻤어
She was, like, 30,
dark hair, attractive.
혹시 거울이라는 걸
들여다 본게 아니고?
Any chance you were looking into a
bright, shiny thing called a mirror?
혹시 대학교때
사귀던 여자 아냐?
Was it someone you dated in college?
아니, 대학교땐
2명밖에 없었어
No, I only dated two girls
in college...
둘 다 금발머리에
안 이뻤어
both blond, both not attractive.
알아봐야 되겠군
Let me check this out.
- 뭐하는거야?
- 어디 보자
-What are you doing?
-Well, let's see.
혹시 이 여자야?
Okay, is that her?
어머나, 맞아!
Oh, my God, yes!
- 누구야?
- 줄리, 캠프장에서의 여자친구
-Who is she?
-Julie Graff, my camp girlfriend.
자기가 끝냈어?
Did you break up with her?
아니, 아직도 사귀는 중이야
No, we're still together.
두 여름 동안 사귀다가
끝냈어
We went out for two summers
and then I broke up with her.
- 왜?
- 3번째의 여름에
-Why?
-She came back the third summer...
봤을땐 진짜 뚱뚜...
and she'd gotten really fa..
- 뚱뚱하다구?
- 뚱뚱하다고 안 했어
-Fat?
-I did not say fat.
뚱뚜우라고 했지
I said fa..
살쪄서 여자를 차버렸다구?
You broke up with a girl
because she was fat?
그래, 그래
Yeah. Yeah.
오래전 얘기야
아직도 맘에 두고 있대?
But it was a really long time ago.
Does she still feel bad?
그런 것 같은데
Apparently she does.
그런 말 있잖아
'코끼리들은 절대로 안 잊는다'
You know what they say:
"Elephants never forget."
나와 결혼하는 것
행운을 빌게
Seriously, good luck marrying me.
무슨 일이야?
Hey, what's going on?
피비가 모니카의 들러리야
She's Monica's maid of honor.
아랫층 여자 들러리
섰을 때보단 잘 하겠지?
Hope it goes better than the last time
you did it for that girl downstairs.
전에 한 적이 있었다구?
You have been maid of honor before?
바로 이런 이유땜에
거짓말하면 안 돼요
You see? This is exactly why
you shouldn't lie.
안되겠어
내가 들러리야
That's it. I am maid of honor.
- 아니, 내가 할거야
- 왜 네가 해?
-No, I am.
-How come you are?
그만큼 하고 싶어서
거짓말까지 했으니까
Because I cared enough to lie.
결정하는데 내가 도와 줄게
Hey, I could help you decide
who should do it.
오디션을 하면 되잖아
We could have an audition.
들러리 역을 어떻게 잘 소화해
내는지에 따라서 말이야
See how you'd handle
maid-of-honor-type situations.
- 무슨 뜻이야?
- 난 원하는 역이 있으면
-What do you mean?
-When I want a job...
오디션을 해서
내가 가장 잘 맞으면
I audition and if I'm the best
of the people they see...
I get the part.
역을 맡게 되는거야
So, okay, so after this audition,
who decides who gets it?
오디션 다음에
누가 결정하는데?
Oh, me and Ross can be the judges.
로스와 내가 하면 되지
-It's better than us deciding.
-Oh, this is crazy.
- 우리가 하는 것 보단 낫네
- 말도 안 돼
-Can't we just flip a coin?
-No, coins hate me.
- 동전 던져서 결정하면 안 돼?
- 안 돼, 동전은 날 싫어해
Okay, fine. You know what?
We will let Ross and Joey decide.
그래, 좋았어
로스와 조이가 결정하기다
Hi!
안녕!
Ross, sweetie.
로스, 자기야
Hey there, handsome thing.
안녕, 멋진 사나이
Wow, this cologne really is
every bit as good as Giorgio.
선전한대로 향수의 효과가
정말로 대단하네
Hey.
왔냐?
Just brought back your videos.
비디오 돌려주러 온 것뿐이야
Hey, Ross. Look, I think
we need to talk about before.
로스, 전에 있었던 일
얘기 좀 해야 되겠어
No. No, we don't.
아니, 할 필요없어
Yes, we do.
해야 돼
Now, look.
That was the best nap I ever had.
솔직히 그게
내 최고의 낮잠이었어
I don't know what
you're talking about.
무슨 말을 하고 있는지
모르겠다
Come on, admit it.
인정할 건 해라
That was the best nap you ever had.
네 최고의 낮잠이었다고
I've had better.
더 괜찮을때도 있었어
Okay. When?
그래, 언제?
All right! All right!
It was the best nap ever!
알았다, 알았어!
가장 최고의 낮잠이었어!
I said it, okay?
인정했어, 됐냐?
But it's over, Joey!
하지만 끝이야!
I want to do it again.
또 자고 싶어!
We can't do it again.
그럴 순 없어
-Why not?
-Because it's weird!
- 왜 안되는거야?
- 이상하니까!
Fine.
관둬
You want a drink?
마실것 줄까?
-Sure. What do you got?
-Warm milk and Excedrin PM.
- 그래, 뭐 있어?
- 따뜻한 우유에 수면제
챈들러
Chandler.
자기가 누군지 알겠어
I just figured out who you are.
내가 지금 뭐하는지는
알겠어?
Can you figure out what I'm doing?
- 루이스 포슨이야
- 누구?
-You're Louis Posen.
-Who?
5학년때 가장 친한 친구
He was my best friend in fifth grade.
어느날 사귀자고 했다가
거절 당했어
One day, I asked him to be
my boyfriend and he said no.
왜 그랬는지 알아?
Do you know why?
화장실에서 일 볼려고 하는데
자꾸 말시켜서?
Because you kept talking to him while
he was trying to go to the bathroom?
아니, 내가 너무
뚱뚜우하다고...
No, but because he thought
I was too fa..
생각할때마다
기분이 상한단 말이야
Every time I think about it,
I feel as bad as I did then.
줄리한테 사과하면 좋겠어
I really think you should
apologize to Julie.
자기 농담하는거야?
16년 전의 일이야
Honey, are you kidding?
That was like 16 years ago.
난 루이스가 사과한다면
기분이 좋아질거야
It would make me feel better
if Louis apologized to me.
할게, 하지만 경고한다
내가 착한 사람으로 변할지도 몰라
I'll do it. But I warn you,
this may make me a better person.
그건 자기가 사랑에 빠진
사람이 아니라고
And that is not the man
you fell in love with.
Okay, we'll give you hypothetical
maid-of-honor situations.
신부 들러리로서의
상황들을 가장해 봤어
You'll be scored
on a scale of one to ten.
1에서 10까지의
점수를 줄거야
-One being the highest.
-Ten is the highest.
- 1이 가장 높아
- 10이 가장 높지
-Why is 10 the highest?
-Because it's the highest.
- 왜 10이 높은거야?
- 가장 높으니까
Okay, Rachel, you're up first.
레이첼이 시작한다
Situation number one:
You're with Monica.
상황 1번이다
모니카와 있는데
The wedding is about to start
when Monica gets cold feet. Go!
결혼식 직전에
모니카는 겁을 먹는다, 시작!
I don't want to marry Chandler.
챈들러와 결혼하기 싫어
-I've got cold feet.
-It's gonna be okay.
- 겁나는걸
- 괜찮아
One man the rest of my life?
I don't know.
한 남자와 평생을 산다?
모르겠어
This means I'll never
get to sleep with Joey.
조이와는 자 볼 수 없잖아
Look, Monica...
잘 들어봐, 모니카
getting cold feet is very common.
겁먹는 것은 흔한 일이야
It's just because
of all the anticipation.
기대감땜에 그런거야
And you just have to remember
that you love Chandler.
넌 챈들러를 사랑한다는 걸
기억하면 돼
And also, I ran out on a wedding.
결혼식장에서
도망 나와봐서 아는데
You don't get to keep the gifts.
선물은 다 돌려줘야 돼
Drawing on your own experience.
개인의 경험을 이용한다...
Very good.
아주 잘했어
Yes, very nice, Rachel.
그래
잘했어요, 레이첼
Thank you, judges.
고맙습니다, 심판님들
-Kiss ass.
-Oh.
- 아첨꾼
- 참나
-Okay, Phoebe.
-Yes, Your Honor.
- 피비
- 네, 선생님
We're now in the ceremony.
결혼식장이야
Monica is about to say, "I do"...
'네'하기 직전인데
when her drunk uncle
starts yelling.
술에 취한 삼촌이
소리를 지르기 시작한다
What do you do? Go!
어떻게 할건가, 시작!
When Monica was a little girl...
모니카가 어렸을때...
I remember that..
기억나는게 있는...
Ow!
아야!
-Very good!
-Oh.
- 엄청 잘했어!
- 좋아라
Yes, excellent. Perfect score.
멋졌어요, 만점
She just made a scene
in the middle of the ceremony!
식장에서
큰 소란을 피웠잖아!
Hey, you want
a little taste of Phoebe?
야, 맛좀 보고 싶은거냐?
신부 들러리로서
연설을 할 시간이다
It is time for you to give
your maid-of-honor speech.
준비 못했는데...
We haven't even prepared..
- 시작!
- 알았어
-Go!
-Okay, okay, okay.
결혼이란 것은
사전에 의하면...
Webster's Dictionary
defines marriage as..
아니, 취소! 시시했어
다시 시작할래
Okay, no! Forget that! That sucks!
Okay, never mind. Forget it.
우리가 6살때
모니카와 처음 만났어요
I met.. I met Monica when we were
just a couple of 6-year-olds...
챈들러는
25살때 친구가 됐구요
and became friends with Chandler
when he was 25...
6살된 아이처럼
행동은 하지만
although he seemed
like a 6-year-old.
맞아
Oh.
고맙습니다
Thank you. Thank you very much.
개인적으로도 알고
커플로서도 압니다
I've known them
separately and together.
둘이 같이 있으면 사랑의 자리에
있는 것을 느낄 수가 있습니다
To know them as a couple is to know
that you are in the presence of love.
이제 잔을 들어서
건배를 하겠습니다
So I would like to raise my glass...
모니카와 챈들러를 위하여
to Monica and Chandler...
또한 새로 시작하는
아름다운 삶을 위하여
and the beautiful adventure they
are about to embark upon together.
이 두 사람만큼
준비된 커플이 없을 겁니다
I can think of no two people
better prepared for the journey.
좋은데
Wow.
- 멋진 연설이었어
- 정말이야
-Great speech.
-Yeah, it really was.
고마워
Oh, thanks.
피비, 네 차례다
해봤자지만...
Okay, Phoebe, I guess you're next.
Although I really don't see the point.
좋았어
Okay.
모니카와 챈들러가 결혼한다는게
믿어지지가 않아요
I can't believe that Monica
and Chandler are getting married.
레이첼과 이 날에 관해서
얘기한 적 있어요
I remember talking
about this day with Rachel...
샤워를 같이 하면서요
벗은 채였죠
while we were
showering together, naked.
게임이 다시 시작됐구먼!
And she's back in the game!
줄리, 안녕
Julie. Hi.
챈들러 빙, 기억나지
Chandler Bing.
I guess you remember me.
안녕, 더러운 속옷
Hello, Skidmark.
별명인데 나중에 설명할게
It's a nickname. I'll explain later.
설명 필요 없어
It's pretty clear.
기한이 지나치게 넘은
사과를 할게
I owe you a long, overdue apology.
네가 살쪄서
너를 차버리는 것이 아니었어
I shouldn't have broken up with you
because of your weight.
그래서 끝낸거였어?
That's why you broke up with me?
몰랐어?
You didn't know that?
그럼, 이만 가볼게
Well, I guess my work here is done.
'센트럴 퍼크'
First of all, I would like to say
you both performed very well, okay?
우선 말을 하는데
둘 다 아주 잘 해냈어
You should be proud.
자랑스러워 할 만해
And I'd also like to say, in this
competition, there are no losers.
이 경쟁에선
실패자란 없는거야
Well, except Rachel. Damn it!
레이첼은 제외하고
제기랄!
Really? I won.
정말이야? 내가 이겼어?
-What?
-I'm sorry, Rach, it was really close.
- 뭐야?
- 미안해, 아슬아슬했어
-Well, then I demand a recount!
-Actually, it wasn't that close.
- 그럼 다시 생각해봐!
- 사실은 아슬아슬하지 않았어
You know what?
Your thing was so stupid anyway.
너희들 방식은 엉망이야
We're gonna flip a coin, all right?
동전 던지기야, 알았지?
Heads.
머리
What? The coins have
finally forgiven me!
드디어 동전들이
날 용서했구나!
Know what? I hope Monica
forgives you after you throw her...
모니카가 너를
용서하길 바랄게
vegetarian-voodoo-goddess-circle-y
shower.
네가 해줄 이상하고
으시시한 선물파티 때문에!
Rach, it's gonna be okay.
You guys are the best!
레이첼, 괜찮을거야
너희들 최고야!
Boy, I tell you. That judging stuff
took a lot out of me.
심판하는거 정말 피곤하다
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
- 그래?
- 그렇다니까
Thinking about maybe going upstairs
and taking a little nap on my couch.
올라가서 소파에서
낮잠이나 잘까 생각중이야
Why would I care about that?
그게 나랑 무슨 상관이야?
No reason. I'm just saying that...
아니, 그냥 알려 주는거야
that's where I'll be.
내가 있을 곳이라구
As bad as that went,
I actually enjoyed myself.
안 좋게 됐지만
기분은 좋았어
I think that I'm going to apologize
for all the stupid things that I do.
이제부터 바보짓 할때마다
사과해야지
Why don't you just stop
doing stupid things?
바보짓을 처음부터
하지말지, 그래?
-Then you wouldn't have to apologize.
-I'd love it if I could do both.
- 그럼 사과할 필요 없잖아
- 둘 다 하고 싶은걸
All right, I have to ask.
안되겠는데
물어 봐야 되겠어
What?
뭔데?
Will you break up with me
if I get fat?
내가 또 뚱뚱해지면
나랑 헤어질거야?
What?
뭐라구?
You broke up with Julie.
How much weight did she gain?
줄리를 찼잖아
쪘으면 얼마나 쪘겠어?
A hundred and forty-five pounds.
65kg 쪘었어
In one year?
한 해에?
My God, what did she eat?
Her family?
세상에, 뭘 먹었길래?
가족?
That's not the point.
그게 문제가 아니야
I know it was a stupid reason to
break up with someone, but I was 15.
그런 이유로 끝내는 것은
잘못이지만 15살이었잖아
Yeah, well, that's not
the only time this was an issue.
그 일 뿐만이 아니라
다른 사건도 있었어
You remember when you spent
Thanksgiving with us?
우리 가족과
추수 감사절 보낸 기억나?
You called me fat.
나를 뚱보라고 했어
Wait a minute.
잠깐만
-That was totally different.
-How?
- 그건 다르지
- 어째서?
You were not supposed to hear that.
I said that behind your back.
네가 들으라고 한 소리가 아니야
너 없는데서 했거든
What if I have babies, okay?
I'm gonna look different.
아이를 갖게 되면?
내 몸매는 달라질거야
I'm okay with that,
but I'm not sure you are.
난 괜찮은데
자기는 안 그럴것 같애
You have to realize I don't think
of you as a thin, beautiful woman.
자기를 날씬하고
아름다운 여자로 안 봤어
This is one of the things that
I can apologize for later.
아까 말했듯이 이 말을
나중에 사과하면 되는거라구
What I mean is, you're Monica.
내 말은
자기는 모니카야
Okay? And I am in love with Monica.
난 모니카한테 빠진거라구
Keep going.
계속 말해봐
So you can balloon up
or you can shrink down...
살이 많이 찌던
쪼그라 들던간에
and I will still love you.
항상 사랑할거야
Even if I were to shrink down
to 2 inches tall?
5cm로 쪼그라들어도?
I'd carry you around in my pocket.
주머니에 넣고 다니지
I love you.
사랑해
Skidmark still got a way
with the ladies.
더러운 속옷이
여자한테서의 인기는 여전하군
Hi, Phoebe.
피비, 안녕
-Hi.
- 안녕
I just want to apologize.
사과하고 싶어
I'm really sorry I was a baby.
애처럼 굴어서 미안해
That's ridiculous.
Rachel, we were all babies once.
사과할 필요없어
우리 모두 다 애였지
Oh, you mean today. Yeah.
오늘 있었던 일 말하는 거구나
Yeah, and you know,
you deserve to win.
네가 할 자격이 있어서
이긴거야
And I was thinking about it.
그리고 생각한건데
If you're Monica's maid of honor,
I get to be yours.
넌 모니카의 들러리면
난 네 들러리잖아
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah.
- 그러네
- 그렇다니까
When Monica and Chandler got engaged,
I put some stuff together.
모니카와 챈들러가 약혼했을때
모으기 시작한거야
-Just in case.
-Oh, that's so sweet. Thanks.
- 혹시나 해서
- 착하기도 해라, 고마워
Here is a book of poetry
that I know Monica loves.
모니카가 좋아하는 시집이야
Oh, God, this is funny. Look.
웃긴건데, 한 번 봐봐
Here's a picture from one Halloween
when she dressed up as a bride.
한 번은 할로윈때
걔가 신부 의상을 입었어
She made me carry her train...
치마 꼬리를 내가 들어줬지
which was weird
because I was Wonder Woman.
좀 웃겼지
난 원더우먼 차림이었거든
Oh, and here's
a little purse that I found.
이건 작은 주머니야
I just thought they could hold
the rings in there.
반지를 넣을 수 있을 것 같아서
-Oh.
-Something. And...
- 그러네
- 뭐든 간에, 그리고...
vintage handkerchiefs, you know,
because people cry at weddings.
옛날 손수건이야
결혼식엔 눈물을 흘리잖아
I'm just gonna grab a couple of these.
내가 좀 써야 되겠다
This stuff is great.
정말로 잘 모았다
I forgot this was in here.
이걸 잊을 뻔했네
This was the garter
that I was saving for my wedding.
내가 결혼할 때를 위해서
아끼던 가터야
And I wanted it
to be Monica's "something borrowed."
모니카한테 빌려 주려던 거야
And it's blue.
그리고 파란색이야
Rach, I think that you should be
Monica's maid of honor.
네가 모니카의
신부 들러리를 해라
You do?
그래?
-Why?
-Because I think it means more to you.
- 왜?
- 너한테 더 의미가 있는것 같다
But, Phoebe, honey, you earned it.
하지만 네가 얻은 자리잖아
It's fine.
I mean, this is something...
난 괜찮아
너는 긴 세월동안
that you've been thinking about
since you were, what, 14?
생각해 온 것 같은데
14살때부터인가?
No, I was 10.
I just developed early.
아니, 10살이야
발육이 빨랐을 뿐이야
Man alive!
세상에나!
-Hey, what's going on?
-Hey!
- 무슨 일이야?
- 안녕
We decided Rachel is
going to be your maid of honor.
레이첼을
네 들러리로 결정했어
Oh, that's great!
어머나, 잘 됐다!
Oh, wow. Okay, we really
have to start planning.
빨리 준비 시작해야 돼
I have really specific ideas.
확실한 아이디어들이 있거든
We should meet four times a week.
일주일에
4번은 만나야 되겠지
Come to my place,
we'll get together before work.
출근하기 전에
우리 집으로 와
What do you say, 6:30, my place?
So excited!
우리 집에서 6시 30분?
기대되는구나!
Yeah, okay. You laugh now.
그래, 실컷 웃어라
She's gonna be yours.
앞으로 너의 들러리야
잘 잤다
Great nap.
정말이야
It really was.
지금 뭐하는거야?
What the hell are you doing?
정말!
God!
Excuse me.
실례합니다